[Music]
[âm nhạc]
[Applause]
[Vỗ tay]
Child, My womb is your home, I
Hài Nhi ơi Bụng của mẹ là nhà của con
hope you eat well, I hope
mong sao con ăn khỏe
you play happily. Mother gives you everything, her
mong sao con nô đùa Mẹ Cho Con Tất Cả
youth rushes by, her beauty fades and
tuổi thanh xuân vội vã nhan sắc nhạt
disappears in the mist. So no matter how far you go,
nhòa phai trong suốt Nên hình hài Dù Có
you will always remember home. There, there is your
Đi đâu xa Con vẫn nhớ về nhà Nơi ấy có
mother's love, so tender. My womb is
tình yêu của mẹ thiết tha bụng của mẹ là
your home, a home that gives you peace. My
nhà của con có một ngôi nhà cho con sự
mother, she is your mother.
đô la mẹ cô con đó là mẹ
No matter how far you go, you will always remember home,
Dù Có Đi đâu xa Con vẫn nhớ về nhà
that is your mother. My womb is your home, a home that gives you peace. My mother, she is your home,
đó là mẹ của con bụng của mẹ là nhà của
a home that gives you
con có một ngôi nhà cho con dù Bình ơi
peace. My mother, she is your home, a home that gives you peace. My
ngôi nhà cho con sự bình an
mother, she
mẹ có con
is your home, a home that gives you peace. My mother, she is
có một ngôi nhà cho con sự bình an
your home,
đó là mẹ của con
[Music] My
[âm nhạc]
Child, My womb is your home, I
Hài Nhi ơi Bụng của mẹ là nhà của con
hope you eat well, I
mong sao con ăn khỏe
hope you
mong sao con
play happily. Mother gives you everything, her youth
nô đùa Mẹ Cho Con Tất Cả tuổi thanh xuân
rushes by, her beauty fades and disappears in the
vội vã nhân sắc nhạt nhòa phai trong
mist. So no matter how far you go, you
sương nên hình hài Dù Có Đi đâu xa Con
will always remember home. There, there is your mother's love,
vẫn nhớ về nhà Nơi ấy có tình yêu của mẹ
my womb is your home,
thiết tha bụng của mẹ là nhà của con có
a home that gives you peace.
một ngôi nhà cho con sự bình an
My parents, she is your mother.
cha mẹ của con đó là mẹ của con
No matter how far I go, I will always remember you, my
Dù Có Đi đâu xa Con vẫn nhớ về nhau
mother. Your womb is my home.
đó là mẹ của con bụng của mẹ là nhà của
There is a home that gives me peace, that is you. There is
con có một ngôi nhà cho con sự bình an
there is a home that gives me peace,
có một ngôi nhà cho con sự bình an
that is my mother, that is my mother.
đó là mẹ của con đó là mẹ của con
[Applause]
[Vỗ tay]
There is a home that gives me peace,
có một ngôi nhà cho con sự bình an
that is my mother,
đó là mẹ của con
that is my
đó là mẹ của con đó
mother, that
mẹ của con đó
is
là
my mother.
mẹ của
[Music]
[âm nhạc]